[{"answer": " Whats up, Rachel", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Hey, Sean.  Im really having some problems here in the dorm.  Can I talk t", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Whats up, Rachel", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Of course.  Thats what Im here for.  Whats going on", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Hey, Sean.  Im really having some problems here in the dorm.  Can I talk t", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, I have a couple of major complaints that are really causing me to hate i", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Of course.  Thats what Im here for.  Whats going on", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Thats not good.  Why dont you tell me about what is bothering you, and wel", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Well, I have a couple of major complaints that are really causing me to hate i", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Well, first of all, its my roommate.  I cant stand her.  Shes totally messy an", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Thats not good.  Why dont you tell me about what is bothering you, and wel", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": "0am, s", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Well, first of all, its my roommate.  I cant stand her.  Shes totally messy an", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " As you know, alcohol is strictly prohibited in the dorms, so I will definitely tal", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 35, "question": "0am, s", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " No.  I had never met her before.  We were just assigned roommates", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": " As you know, alcohol is strictly prohibited in the dorms, so I will definitely tal", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Sometimes that can make a difficult match with roomates.  Do you think yo", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 40, "question": " No.  I had never met her before.  We were just assigned roommates", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " No way.  Ive tried talking to her and she just rolls her eyes", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Sometimes that can make a difficult match with roomates.  Do you think yo", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " OK, what I can do is put you on the roommate-switch request list.  It might tak", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 46, "question": " No way.  Ive tried talking to her and she just rolls her eyes", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 50, "question": " OK, what I can do is put you on the roommate-switch request list.  It might tak", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " Is there anything else that was bothering you", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Yes, the room is a big problem too", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Is there anything else that was bothering you", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Really?  Whats wrong with it", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yes, the room is a big problem too", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " It is just so small.  Theres only enough room for two little beds and a table.  It", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Really?  Whats wrong with it", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " OK, well, all of the rooms here in the dorm are the same size so I cant chang", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 59, "question": " It is just so small.  Theres only enough room for two little beds and a table.  It", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " I dont know if I can take it for the whole year living in such a tiny space wit", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 64, "question": " OK, well, all of the rooms here in the dorm are the same size so I cant chang", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Did you make loft beds in your rooms?  Raising the beds off the floor makes ", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 68, "question": " I dont know if I can take it for the whole year living in such a tiny space wit", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Yes, we did, but its still so tiny in there", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Did you make loft beds in your rooms?  Raising the beds off the floor makes ", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " The only other thing I can suggest is moving to a new dorm.  Brumby has bigge", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Yes, we did, but its still so tiny in there", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Could I move over there then?  I dont care about the cost", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " The only other thing I can suggest is moving to a new dorm.  Brumby has bigge", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Im not sure of the availability of the rooms right now, but I can check.  If its full", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Could I move over there then?  I dont care about the cost", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Please, please, check on that for me.  I would really appreciate it.  If nothing i", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 84, "question": " Im not sure of the availability of the rooms right now, but I can check.  If its full", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " All right.  I can do that this week and then get back to you", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Please, please, check on that for me.  I would really appreciate it.  If nothing i", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " How often do rooms usually become available there", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 89, "question": " All right.  I can do that this week and then get back to you", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " It just depends.  Sometimes it can take months, but other times you might ge", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 90, "question": " How often do rooms usually become available there", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Oh, OK", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 94, "question": " It just depends.  Sometimes it can take months, but other times you might ge", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Well try our best to get you moved.  We want you to be happy your first yea", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Oh, OK", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 99, "question": " Well try our best to get you moved.  We want you to be happy your first yea", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " So Ill talk to the RA at the other dorm and have a word with your roommat", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " OK.  That sounds good.  Thank you for your help", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 104, "question": " So Ill talk to the RA at the other dorm and have a word with your roommat", "qSentId": 103},{"answer": " Youre welcome.  See you later", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 105, "question": " OK.  That sounds good.  Thank you for your help", "qSentId": 104},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "05-01", "aSentId": 106, "question": " Youre welcome.  See you later", "qSentId": 105}]
